Guide to the Georg Kreisel Papers SC0136
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Wittgenstein colloquim, 1976 Apr
  - Memos/course notes:
    - “A neglected problem concerning Kleene’s schematic S1-S9" (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - "Update on 2 papers reviewed in MR, 1976" (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - "How Large are Ramsey numbers?" (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Zurich Lecture for Eidgenossiche Technische Hochschule; "Constructivist Approaches to Logic" – paper by Kreisel and related correspondence (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Wittgenstein Lectures – book review for Bull. Of the HMS and related correspondence (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "From Science to Foundations: Justifying and unwinding Proofs." Correspondence re paper and symposium for which it was intended (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Elementary Logic: Some Lessons from the Last 25 Years" (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Informal Rigor and Completeness Proofs" (Box 26, Folder 8)